Wylie Wong collection of May's Studio photographs and San Francisco Chinatown ephemera M1999
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 4. Artwork and Ephemera
  - Man on a horse; traditional style ink drawing with pigment (Flat-box 15, Folder 1)
  - The Young Companion, no. 120, magazine cover, 1936 (Flat-box 15, Folder 2)
  - The Young Companion, no. 124, magazine cover, 1937 (Flat-box 15, Folder 3)
  - Chinese opera, photographs/posters, circa 1980s (Flat-box 15, Folder 4)
  - "The Street of Gamblers"; poster with photograph by Arnold Genthe (Flat-box 15, Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Chinatown map (Flat-box 15, Folder 6)
  - Photocopy of scrapbook with images of Chinese opera and clippings (Flat-box 15, Folder 8)
  - Chinatown Beatification Project poster (Flat-box 16, Folder 6)
  - Chan is Missing, movie poster; signed by filmmaker, Wayne Wong, 1981 (Flat-box 16, Folder 7)
  - "San Francisco, drawn after nature" (1852); printed by Strawberry Hill Press, San Francisco, 1975 (Flat-box 16, Folder 8)
  - Philip Chan, bamboo photograph (Flat-box 16, Folder 10)
  - "Scene from the Spectacle of Sun and Moon"; engraving (visual work) (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - "The Culture and Preparation of Tea"; engraving (visual work) (Box 17, Folder 3)
  - Hong Kong Chinese opera poster, circa 1960s (Map-folder 38)
  - Miscellaneous Chinese art/ephemera (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Wylie Wong, business cards (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Lotus and Sun, print (visual work); no. 15/165, signed by the artist, 1974 (Map-folder 37)
  - The Radiant Maiden, playbill, 1983 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Poster for "Last Emperor" opera performance (Map-folder 39)
  - "Pear Garden in the West"; poster advertising "America Chinese Theater, 1852-1983" Exhibition and performances (original photograph used for the poster, "Ch'i-hsing-teng as a woman warrior" is in box 1, folder 2) (Flat-box 15, Folder 7)
  - "Pear Garden in the West"; program for Chinese American performing arts festival, 1984 (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - "Pear Garden in the West"; program for Chinese American performing arts festival, 1986 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Series 5. Publications
  This small series contains photo copies of books related to the history of Chinese Theater, particularly Chinese theater in America.
  - With New Eyes: Toward an Asian American Art History in the West; photocopy of cover of exhibit catalog, 1995 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - The Chinese Theatre: A Brief Consideration by George Kin Leung; photocopy of book (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - The History of Cantonese Opera in San Francisco, California (1852-1941) by William C. Hu; photocopy of book draft (Box 17, Folders 11-13)